Welcome to Beauty Revolution!
- Mommy! The show is just starting. Come!
- Coming!
…Beauty Revolution.
A leader in this country's
cosmetic surgery industry,
and a renowned surgeon,
referred to by all as "The Hand of God,"
please welcome the director
of Tohyama Cosmetic Surgery Clinic,
Dr. Arata Tohyama!
- Thank you for being here.
- Mommy! Look, it's Daddy!
Yes!
Everyone, since this is
the very first episode of our show,
we'd like to tell you
a bit more about Dr. Tohyama.
Now, just take a look at this.
BEFORE
Ladies and gentlemen, do any of you
recognize the person in this picture?
Well, believe it or not,
this is actually a picture
of Dr. Tohyama himself.
- What?
- No?!
- So, that's really your face?
- Yes.
I performed the surgery on myself,
with the help of The Hand of God.
- Yes, that's right.
- Wow!
Isn't that just incredible?
- I would never have guessed.
- Is that true?
Just incredible!
I'm still having trouble believing it!
Really amazing.
DAD
Mm… What's happening?
Oh, sorry.
It's all right. Don't get up.
PLEASE TAKE A LOOK WHEN YOU HAVE TIME
PROPOSAL ON FUTURE MANAGEMENT POLICY
Oh!
I'm sorry, Fumi.
Uh, I should have paid closer attention.
Seriously, just lay off and let me drink.
It's just alcohol.
Huh?
How come you won't listen?
I've told you, cirrhosis is irreversible,
which means that your damaged liver
will never go back to normal,
so you can't drink
any alcohol at all, Mom!
- How many times do I have to say it?
- You don't need to say it again.
So now you're "Tanuma?"
A senior doctor
at a private practice covered it, huh?
God, you're a liar.
It's still not okay
for you to drink alcohol.
A decent person
would never do plastic surgery at all!
Yeah, well, I didn't want to do it either!
But somehow, I got saddled
with your husband's debt,
so I don't really have a choice!
God, I'm sorry. I really am!
And either way,
you haven't got the right
to a say in my life.
Got it?
You can't do anything at all.
So don't act like you're better than me.
TOHYAMA COSMETIC SURGERY CLINIC
DOCTOR TANUMA
Hi, my subjects. I'm a princess!
My name's Princess Moenon. Princess Pose!
Oh, that's wonderful!
So sweet!
Your eyes
are starting to look like Mommy's.
- You think so?
- Yeah.
Princess Moenon,
Daddy says you look like Mommy.
Mama!
- Mama!
- Oh, good job!
Lovely!
DAUGHTERS
Moeno, should we start shooting?
Mm-hmm. Be right there.
I want you to perform her surgery.
It can't be me. It has to be you.
What? Ms. Backlash
performed Ms. Yuriko's surgery?
Shh! Don't say it too loudly.
But doesn't that mean
Ms. Backlash is really good, then?
I mean, if The Hand of God
trusted her with a surgery…
It was probably a fluke.
No wonder the nursing team
has been buzzing with gossip.
Why's that?
Well, the director's been making Backlash
her assistant for every surgery lately.
She's even had her
sit in on counselling sessions.
So, they're saying
that this might be special training
to prepare her
to become the director of a new branch.
Like, in Ginza?
No, that can't be.
Doctor, you're getting all red.
Are you jealous?
No, I'm not.
Don't worry, Mr. Rui.
No matter what anyone says,
you're Director Tohyama's right-hand man.
Just think about
how wild your fans are about you, huh?
I know you are.
I looked over the chairman's proposal,
and, as we expected, it seems that
he's against opening the Ginza branch.
I see that.
Oh, by the way,
have you asked the chairman
about the rumor that he's coming back?
- He dodged the question.
- Hm.
But I'll make sure that he doesn't.
If he does come back,
I'll lose my position.
ESTABLISHING A CHILDREN'S CLINIC
Excuse me, but are you Moenon?
Uh, yeah.
No way!
I watched the Moenon Channel all the time!
- Everyone our age watched it.
- Oh! Princess Pose!
Are you in elementary school?
Of course she is! It would be weird
if she were still introducing toys!
Yeah, that's true!
- Can we take a picture with you?
- Oh, sure.
This is so exciting!
All right, Princess Pose!
MOENON'S PRINCESS COOKING
Our videos haven't been doing well
since we switched to cooking tutorials.
I was thinking we could do a collab
with someone famous.
- Like Ryuji?
- Exactly.
Nah, the target audiences don't match.
- Minami, listen.
- Yeah?
Honestly, the way
things are going right now,
I can't even cover
the mortgage on this place.
Well, why did you buy
something in this high-rise then?
Come on. Don't be so harsh.
You know your agency
has benefited from our relationship.
Hey, you know we're grateful
to the Moenon Channel. Of course we are.
We don't have any other channels
with five million subscribers.
- Right?
- Sponsorships were next level.
It's just that kids content
is a tough category.
As soon as they grow up, their character
becomes a bit awkward, right?
You know, it might be good if her persona
went through a drastic change.
- No, no, no.
- That isn't gonna work!
- Why not? It's the…
- Yeah. Exactly.
So tell me,
what's with the cute ribbon, huh?
Welcome home, sis.
Why are you here?
- Oh, hello there.
- Macky quit the loan shark business.
- So he's unemployed.
- Huh?
Oh! It's just that thanks to…
to, uh… to your father's generosity,
I've started working here
as a live-in employee.
- You're living here?
- Yes.
- What?
- It's not what you think, sweetheart.
He had nowhere to go.
He was going to live on the streets.
So I was worried about him, and I offered.
So it's all good. He can sleep in my room.
So sorry.
- Phew! We're safe!
- She's terrifying!
What's up?
Um, it's about Mom.
She hasn't come out of her room
all morning.
She's not a kid. Just leave her alone.
Why does Mom hate plastic surgery so much?
She's old-fashioned.
And close-minded.
What do you think of it?
- Hm?
- Getting work done.
My opinion is, if they wanna do it,
that's on them.
I'm not like Mom, you know?
I'm not gonna interfere
in other people's lives.
- Okay.
- Yeah.
What is it?
Well, I've been thinking
about getting double eyelids.
You better not!
Dumbass! Why would you do that?
You can't.
Seriously, come on!
Why would you do that, Takeru?
- I'd look better with them.
- You look good right now.
Just squeeze it out, like that.
Kinda looks like a snake.
It's gonna be good.
Moenon Beam!
Shine! Voilà!
It's gonna taste…
- Hey, Minami.
- …even better.
Yeah.
What?
Hello, everyone. Right now,
I'm on my way to somewhere exciting.
Can you guess where?
I know it's hard to tell.
All right, we're finally here!
Ta-da!
Today, I'm at the clinic
of Dr. Rin Tohyama,
who's known as "The Hand of God."
I'm so excited!
The plan is for the surgeries
to happen over summer break.
We'd follow her transformation in a series
of videos until school starts back up.
MOENON'S BEAUTIFUL PRINCESS PROJECT
That's the idea.
I've told Moeno
that it'll be a full makeover,
so you can have all the freedom
to do whatever you want to.
It's quite risky, though, don't you think?
Didn't a parent get backlash recently
for making their daughter
have plastic surgery?
Yeah. But, actually,
some backlash would be good for us--
Sure, it works for you, but not for us.
I'm sure you see that there are tons
of videos of kids doing hair removal
and taking all types of surgeries.
If we end up doing this,
we want it to really make an impact.
Look how big it is!
Hi, I'm Moeno!
- Thank you so much for having me!
- Hi there.
- Hello there, everyone.
- Hello.
- You two are so pretty.
- Another video shoot?
- Ah, it really takes me back.
My daughter used to love watching
the Moenon Channel when she was little.
Huh? That girl is Moeno?
Yeah, it's a pretty bold move
for the director.
Really?
In order to proceed, I need to confirm
how willing the child is,
beyond the patient's consent.
This will put
a huge amount of strain on her body,
so I need to discuss the procedures
with the patient,
to see how far she wants to go with them.
Also, Chairman Tohyama gave me a quote
for the advertising fees.
He said it was roughly this much.
Is that right?
Uh… Huh?
That amount reflects expenses
for advertising the full package deal.
However, after I speak with the patient,
the number of procedures could be reduced,
along with the price.
Right. I see.
Yeah, I think she'll probably
want to go through with all of it.
100 MILLION YEN
Absolutely not.
You can count me out on this one.
I thought you might feel that way.
I do. Now, excuse me.
You'll still be
performing the surgery with me.
I told you. I don't want to.
Why are you being so negative?
I don't wanna do that to a child.
There are lots of children out there
who get braces or piercings
or do hair removal.
Age has nothing
to do with wanting to be beautiful.
Yeah, except this kind of surgery is--
I can't believe you're still acting
like plastic surgery is taboo.
I'm going to change
your old-fashioned, rigid way of thinking.
It's gonna be good for you.
Excuse me.
Director, Moenon's in the counseling room.
I'll handle the intake counseling.
Dr. Numata, look up some examples
of pediatric plastic surgery.
What's the matter this time?
Sulking again?
Didn't I warn you?
Being stubborn will only
make things harder for you.
Can I ask you something?
Hm? Oh.
Mr. Hikita, you've got
a daughter, don't you?
Yeah. I've got three of 'em.
What if your daughters
decided they wanted
to get plastic surgery?
Huh. Well, I wouldn't want them
to look like me,
so I guess I'd say yes. Hm.
All right. I've got a good sense
of what you want to look like.
So we'll start
as soon as summer break begins.
Yes! Thank you very much.
Okay, now, shake hands. Shake.
- Hm. Thank you very much.
- Thank you so much.
Over here!
Cut! Okay, that is a wrap, ladies.
- Thank you again.
- Thank you.
- Doctor, you were perfect. Great job.
- Uh, listen, sir?
- Yes?
Could you please give us a moment?
Huh?
I'd like to have a final consultation
with her in private.
Oh. Uh, of course.
I'll leave you to it.
- Thank you.
- See you.
See you soon.
For the next few minutes,
just forget about your videos.
I want to know what you think of all this,
and I want you to be honest.
Okay.
Moeno, listen.
Do you really want me
to perform this operation?
- I have another question for you.
- What?
Well, it's uh…
It's about Ms. Yuriko.
I performed some of her procedure.
Uh-huh.
And, you know,
the director is a skilled surgeon.
- Mm.
- So, I wondered why she asked me to do it.
Ah, you want me
to answer that for you, huh?
Look, Dr. Numata,
it's because you
are one of the dark side people now.
So now you know why.
- Bon appétit!
- Bon appétit.
- Mmm.
- Mmm!
- Oh, that's good.
- We haven't come here in a while.
- Yeah.
I hope we can become regulars again.
Yeah.
Hey, what did you discuss earlier?
- Hm?
With Dr. Rin, I mean.
Ah. She asked if I was really okay
with doing all the surgeries.
I said, "Of course I'm okay
with it. I trust you, and I trust my dad."
So, you're sure you are?
Hey, why are you asking me that too?
I was the one who said
I wanted to do all the surgeries.
You're right. You did.
Yeah.
I can't believe I'm so lucky.
I get to have Dr. Rin do my surgery,
and I get paid for it.
It's totally gonna go viral!
That's right.
Yeah.
- Hey, chef. Another, please?
- Sure.
You're having more?
Huh? Why not?
It's been ages since
I've had such good news. I'm celebrating.
Oh, here it is.
Yes!
You know, these days,
elementary school kids
getting plastic surgery
is becoming as normal as getting a pet.
Yeah, but still,
when parents or agencies are behind it,
I dunno, it sort of feels like kids are
being sacrificed for profit or something.
Sacrificed? Come on now.
It's not like they're selling off
their organs or anything, right?
Look, I think it's normal
for kids to wanna look cute.
You might be getting
too worked up about this.
Sure, I'm getting worked up.
Now my little brother's saying
that he wants to get double eyelids.
Mm, sure, why not?
Guys getting plastic surgery is normal.
Wait, no, I'm telling you,
my brother is perfect as he is.
I should probably just talk to her myself
and convince her not to do it.
No, come on, don't do it.
That would be such a boomer move.
People always tell me
I seem older than I am.
Mm.
Hello.
Oh, hi.
- Good job, honey.
- Hey, look at this.
This girl's been in internet videos
since she was tiny.
This one has six million views.
Moeno, what do you want to be
when you grow up?
- Mama!
- What?
So sweet.
Thank you.
I guess people want to watch this.
Thank you. Looks yummy.
Good morning.
Hey, it's Tohyama.
Hey, Tohyama. Your dad
was on TV yesterday, right?
- "Trust in The Hand of God."
- So cool!
- Nailed it!
- He was.
I knew it! So cool.
Wait, is it true?
Did he really do his own plastic surgery?
My mom said it was just for TV
and it wasn't true.
I think that you're beautiful,
and you look just like your dad!
But isn't that weird?
If his real face is actually ugly,
then why is his daughter cute?
That means you had plastic surgery too.
No, I didn't.
You did! If you look like his face now,
then you must have had it done too.
Yeah!
Plastic surgery!
Plastic surgery! Plastic surgery!
I saw your stream yesterday.
I'm so jealous that you're getting surgery
with Dr. Tohyama!
- Totally.
- Me too!
Are you getting your eyes done?
I can't tell you yet. It's still a secret.
- Aw, come on, tell us!
- I want surgery too.
- Really?
- Are you getting it during summer break?
Yeah. I'm going to the clinic again today
for another check-up.
That's so cool.
Going up. Stand clear of the doors.
Oh, I'm sorry! Come in.
The doors are open.
Uh, what floor do you want?
The fourth floor.
Are you sure? The fourth floor
is the cosmetic surgery clinic.
Yes, I'm sure.
Oh.
Sorry about that.
This is the fourth.
Is Dr. Rui still with a patient?
He's got two more after this.
We'll get complaints if he's late.
- True.
- What's--
Ms. Todoroki.
- Uh, this is--
- Oh, Ms. Konoike, you're here.
We've been expecting you.
I'm Miss Todoroki.
Here, take my hand.
This way, Miss.
Ms. Konoike is here.
Ms. Konoike is
one of the director's special clients.
- I do hope that you weren't rude to her.
- I wasn't!
You know, the way you said that was rude!
Excuse me.
Sara!
Hello there.
So, what can I do for you today?
I got a little bored.
- With what?
- I don't like my nose.
I wanna make it a bit sharper.
- Hm.
- Looks fine to me.
She wants a nasal-tip-plasty.
Her setup's almost done.
Again? I thought she just had one.
- We'd better hurry.
- Right.
Ah! Oh, thank goodness
you're here, Dr. Numata.
Moenon needs to do her pre-op tests,
but the director got pulled
into an unscheduled surgery.
- Right now?
- Yes. We need you!
Squeeze your thumb.
Very good. Here we go.
This might sting a little bit.
- Mm.
- There. All done.
Now this won't hurt at all.
That's 4 cc in.
Ms. Konoike?
She's under, Doctor.
All right.
Please call him in.
Please come in.
Can you put pressure right here for a bit?
Okay.
Why don't we swap?
- Press right here.
- Okay.
Moeno, do you mind if I
ask you a question?
Sure.
Did they give you
a thorough explanation of the surgeries?
Your body's still
in the process of growing,
which means your bone structure
will keep changing.
So, if you really want to do it, you might
want to wait until you're a bit older--
It's okay.
I wanna do it right away.
Dr. Rin told me the same things
that you just said.
But if I wait until I'm older,
it'll be too late.
Honestly, I don't even want to wait
till summer break.
I'd do it today if I could.
I see.
A nurse should come soon. Just wait here.
Okay.
Mr. Hikita?
Moeno, look!
- We're getting a huge amount of views!
- Oh yeah?
Yeah.
- Yay!
- Oh yeah!
- Yeah! Princess Pose!
- Princess Pose!
- We got this, yes!
- Oh, good!
This is it.
- Hold on a second.
- Yeah, I think this is finally it.
Hello?
- Oh, Auntie?
- I came for a visit.
- Okay, I'll buzz you in.
- Thanks.
Sorry for dropping in suddenly.
I was just in the neighborhood.
- It's been a while.
- Thank you for having me.
Mm-hmm. There.
- It really has been a while.
- Yes.
This is lovely.
- Come on in.
- Hello.
Oh, Kaoru.
- You're leaving?
- Just for a bit.
I thought we could have dinner together.
I, yeah, just, uh, got called
to a meeting suddenly.
So don't worry about me.
Make yourself comfortable.
- All right. I'll take you up on that.
- Great. Then I'll see you later.
- Bye.
- Good luck.
Thanks. See you.
I did bring enough takeout for three,
though, so we'll just have to eat it.
It's from Isetan! It looks delicious.
Would you look at that mess?
Why don't we do a little cleaning first?
- We'll do it together.
- Well…
This is awful!
I'm clocking out now too.
- Huh?
- Hope you had a good day.
Thanks. You too.
God, it's really hot, huh?
It's not that bad.
- You don't feel thirsty from this heat?
- Mm-mm.
Huh? Wait.
- You want me to invite you out?
- Yeah.
Is that so? Hm.
- Let's go.
I know you're awake in there, Mom.
You should try to eat something at least.
Can you hear me, Mom?
Mm, this is delicious.
- You like it?
- Mm.
Good.
- Eat as much as you want.
- Thanks.
Mm.
Auntie? What is it? What's wrong?
Mm, I was… thinking about how much
you're starting to look like your mom.
- Really?
- Yeah.
Hm.
I'm sure you're gonna grow
into a beautiful woman just like her.
But if your mom was
still with us, I think she'd be shocked.
Moeno, you became famous so quickly
through those videos,
and now you're living in this huge,
fancy apartment right downtown.
Well, yeah, because of Dad.
Yes, of course.
Your father used to work
in the television industry after all.
But I still never thought he'd quit
and go all in on video streaming.
Come on, Auntie. Don't say it like that.
If Dad heard, he'd be mad.
You're right. Sorry.
Hey, Moeno, honey,
I wanted to ask you something important.
Mm.
Would you like to come and live with me?
What?
Could I please have another one?
- Right away.
- Thanks.
Hey, this is a pretty modest place
for someone who earns as much as you do.
My oldest daughter
is repeating a year at med school.
My second daughter's taking a gap year
to get into med school.
And my third daughter is a total recluse.
Those girls have cleaned me out.
Must be tough.
You wanted to talk?
- Might as well get straight to the point.
- Mm.
The surgery for that Konoike person.
You performed it, right?
- Thanks for your patience.
- Right, thank you.
First, can I finish this drink?
Hey there, Mom!
I'm gonna come in now.
Uh, Mom?
Excuse me, Director.
Sorry to disturb. You have a visitor.
A visitor now?
She said that she's Dr. Numata's mother.
Don't say weird
and random stuff like that, Auntie.
It's not random. I'm serious, Moeno.
Uh, but then… what about my dad?
Well, that's just it.
I need to have
a real discussion with your father.
- Hm.
- But think about it, Moeno.
My family and I,
we were all quite shocked,
and I mean truly shocked,
when I saw that you were doing a series
on getting plastic surgery.
Honestly, we've been worried about you
for a while,
but we trusted your father,
and decided to leave you in his care.
- But we can't take any more of it.
- This is something I want, though.
We've already consulted with a lawyer.
They made it clear that forcing your child
to have plastic surgery
and streaming it online is child abuse--
I told you. I was the one
who wanted to do it!
He should stop you. It's his job!
I want you to convince her to quit.
I'll pay back all the money
you covered for her,
even if I have to take out
another loan or something.
Just please
make her quit.
Uh…
I don't understand.
Why exactly do you want her
to quit so much?
Well, because I'm her mom,
obviously,
and she's my daughter.
And I want to protect her
from all you people.
A medical accident?
You saw the Konoike girl, right?
She went blind
because of a mistake during a procedure.
The director performed the surgery.
It was a complicated procedure.
A combination of submental liposuction
and midface fat grafting.
Ms. Konoike.
- Ms. Konoike!
- Should we call the doctor?
- Yes.
- Ms. Konoike, can you hear me?
- Doctor.
- She's still unconscious?
We might need an ambulance.
She's not waking up.
Sara, hon?
Sara, can you hear me? Sara, wake up.
Sara!
She seems all right. Thank goodness.
Sara,
how are you feeling?
My eyes.
What about your eyes?
Why can't I see?
I can't see.
Her grandfather
has been a patron of the Tohyama Clinic
ever since the former director,
Chairman Tohyama, founded it.
The director was responsible
for an extremely important person's
granddaughter going blind.
And that's when she started to change.
What changed?
Well, during similar surgeries…
Uh…
I mean the ones
that required general anesthesia.
She couldn't seem
to hold a scalpel properly anymore.
So then,
she's got the yips?
Most probably.
So that's why
she needs surgeons like us.
The dark side.
I see.
I'd like you to leave.
Regardless of your wishes,
if Dr. Numata decides to resign,
then I'll speak with her personally.
What are you plotting?
You think I'm plotting?
You covered 200 million yen
and hired Fumi just like that?
I want to know
what the hell you've got going on!
Ma'am, please, we will speak
directly to Dr. Numata ourselves.
Just shut up!
Your kind think
you can buy people's lives with money,
and then treat them
like they're just trash.
My daughter is precious,
and I refuse to let people like you
take her hostage!
You can go now.
We'll speak to Dr. Numata directly.
Come, ma'am. It's time to go now.
Come on, this way.
- Let go of me! Get off me!
- Please calm down, ma'am.
- Otherwise, we'll call the police.
- Stop!
Go ahead and call them.
Give me my Fumi back!
- Calm down!
- Let go of me!
You're a fraud!
- Give her to me!
- Stop it now!
- Stop it!
- Fumi is mine! Give her back!
- Give me my Fumi!
- Yes, all right. We understand.
Right? All right?
- Damn you.
- Come on.
Get out of here.
Moeno,
sweetheart, this is for your own good.
Yeah, well, I never asked you to do this!
- I had to. It would have been too late!
- I'm not gonna do it!
I'm never gonna leave Dad!
When Mom was sick and dying,
my dad took care of her all by himself.
And then he had to raise me all alone.
Do you know how hard it was for him?
Do you know how much he's suffered?
That doesn't mean it's okay
for him to make money off your videos.
It's not something a parent--
Get out!
Don't say that about him!
You never cared about me!
Don't act like you care
all of a sudden. Get out!
Get out!
Don't ever come back here!
Now that girl
has the director at her beck and call.
And apparently, she also paid a hefty sum
to keep them quiet.
If the chairman got wind of it,
it would be over for her.
Well, isn't the chairman retired though?
What's the big deal?
That's what he wants people to think.
He's a sort of the wizard
behind the curtain.
You've heard of that kid?
- The kid who wants to get plastic surgery?
- Yeah.
They say the chairman's
pushing hard for it.
DIRECTOR
No. No, no. Don't worry about that.
Hello. This is Dr. Numata.
Don't you ever send your mother
to the clinic ever again.
I'm sorry, what?
My mother? What are you talking about?
Grow up.
You're not a kid anymore.
One, two!
Come with me.
Why the hell
did you pull a stunt like that?
What the hell's gotten into you, Fumi?
You'll disturb the customers.
I want you
to stop interfering with my life!
Tell me the truth.
Aren't you ashamed of having
people like that push you around all day?
What?
You've let men push you around
my whole life, and you're judging me?
Remind me who's responsible
for saving this house?
- Quit acting like I owe you.
- Huh?
I would rather die homeless on the streets
than take a single cent
from people who profit off desire!
So go ahead and die!
But don't you dare ruin Takeru's life!
How's he gonna go to college
when you're 200 million yen in debt, huh?
Answer me!
You have no right to butt in
and screw it all up
when you can't even do a damn thing
for my brother!
Quit acting like you know
anything about it!
- Shut the hell up!
- Stop it!
I've had enough of this.
I'm not going to go to college
if you're gonna fight all day long.
Huh?
Who cares if we're poor?
Listen, Takeru, it's not like that.
Stop lying to me!
You're working at that clinic
for my sake, right?
Just quit already, would you?
That way, Mom will be satisfied,
and it'll all be settled.
- Okay, so, your surgery starts tomorrow?
- Mm.
So this is the last time
we'll see your face like this?
Uh, yeah. It looks like I won't be able
to go to the pool this summer.
- Oh, really?
- Mm.
Oh, hey, should we all go
take photos together now.
- Yeah, yeah, yeah!
- Yeah!
How was it last night?
Did you have a nice time with your family?
Look, I…
I have nothing to do with my parents.
Good to hear.
It's important to be independent,
Dr. Numata.
Yes, it is.
It's crazy to think
that some adults over the age of 30
still care about their parents' approval.
Are you talking about me?
Did it come across like that?
I mean, I'm sure someone like you
would never just do
what your parents told you to, right?
Dr. Numata, your patient's here.
Coming.
Are you my real daddy?
Why are you asking me that?
Everyone is saying we don't look alike.
Ah, I understand.
Because they watched the TV program.
Come here.
Hm.
Listen to me.
No matter what anyone else says,
you are my precious daughter.
My one and only daughter, sweetheart.
But then, what's actually true?
The truth doesn't matter.
It doesn't matter
if we don't look alike, right?
Because you are
the one and only daughter I have.
What?
Hey, don't make that face.
Smile.
That's good. You know, Rin?
I love that smile of yours.
And when I see you smile,
it energizes me, and I can work harder.
So I would like you
to always be smiling for Daddy.
That's good.
That's it.
CUTE
PRINCESS POSE
I was thinking about how much
you're starting to look like your mom.
Hi! Let's get started.
It's been really hot outside.
How are you all doing?
Let's see how many viewers are with us.
Wow! Almost 2,000 people
are watching this live. That's great!
Ah, hello, everyone!
This is the Tohyama Clinic team!
Welcome!
Wow, what an amazing welcome.
Thank you so much for having me!
Hi there!
ARATA TOHYAMA
BUY AND SEND ¥50,000
Thank you!
I'm having my first surgery today,
and I'm pretty nervous,
but I'm going to be brave.
Everyone together now…
Princess Pose!
THE CHAIRMAN! IS HE WATCHING?
Wow! Everyone can do it.
That's so amazing!
MOENO SURGERY SCHEDULE
So, the whole package, huh?
- She said it's what she wanted.
- Director, Ms. Konoike's on the phone.
She said it's an emergency and she wants
you to go to her house right now.
What? Stop the live stream?
Impossible. We already
have tons of viewers.
If we cut it now, it'll kill us.
An emergency patient
has just come in, I'm afraid.
Can we get another doctor
to perform the surgery?
- No.
- We can just focus on the hands.
- What? I'm doing it?
- They can't stop the live stream.
But I can't do that.
Today, it's just a simple
double eyelid operation.
- No, I can't do it on such short notice.
- There's no time to argue.
What exactly are you afraid of?
That this Konoike person
is going to expose what happened?
Doctors make mistakes.
It happens all the time.
This is all happening because
you tried to cover it up, isn't it?
Just the other day, you told me
that I'm not a kid anymore.
What about you?
You're so worried
about your dad's approval.
You know,
I thought you were
a lot more independent than that.
- Uh, Director--
- I'll be back as soon as I can.
- Try to keep the live stream going.
- I'll have the car brought.
Hi, everyone. I'm Dr. Rui.
How are you all doing?
Hello to all Moeno's fans.
Nice to meet you.
As a surprise,
today I'm gonna do a little collab
with the Moenon Channel!
Moeno and I will have a little chat
before her surgery starts.
It's an honor
to do a collab with you, Dr. Rui.
- Yeah?
- Oh, you're so cool!
- Sara. Sorry I'm late.
- Come on in.
- Alexa, turn on the lights.
- Okay.
Sara, I'm sorry to say this,
but I don't really have much time today.
It's my neck.
It's been hurting since yesterday.
Your neck?
Yes. I wanted you to take a look at it.
I'm sorry Sara, but
I've got a patient
waiting for a surgery right now.
If you need a massage,
I can call one of the nurses--
My eyesight was taken from me.
Did you forget?
I'm sorry. I'm feeling a little nervous.
- Hm.
- Can I go to the restroom?
Of course. It's your first surgery.
Being nervous is normal.
Mm. See you in a minute.
- Yeah, see you.
- Okay.
Uh, okay while Moeno is away,
why don't I start
answering any questions you might have.
I'm sorry.
Mm.
Mom.
I'm sorry.
What exactly are you afraid of?
That this Konoike person
is going to expose what happened?
Sara, I'm sorry.
I really have to go now.
That's strange.
Moeno is taking a pretty long time.
She must be very nervous.
Uh, well, uh, let's see…
While we're waiting for Moeno to get back,
I would like to treat you all to a special
performance of Dr. Rui's juggling act!
Bring Dr. Rui's things to the DC.
Enough.
A massage that bad won't help me anyway.
I'm sorry.
I'll try harder next time.
Don't ever speak to me like that again,
or I'll call Dubai right away.
Excuse me.
Hello?
I understand.
She's on her way now,
so bring Moenon to the O.R.
WHEN'S THE OPERATION?
GIVE US MOENON
It's okay.
Going up. Stand clear of the doors.
GOOD LUCK, MOENON
FINALLY!
OH, IT'S ABOUT TO START
I CAN'T WAIT
The director is coming in.
I'm so sorry to keep you waiting.
It's okay.
I'm in your hands now.
MY HEART'S IN MY MOUTH!
Director?
WHAT ARE HER PARENTS THINKING?
THE TENSION'S THROUGH THE ROOF
The surgery…
…is cancelled.
What?
- What?
- Cancelled?
No. No!
What are you talking about? Are you nuts?
You just made us wait for ages!
Either way, it can't happen.
Our clinic can't perform surgery on her.
Why not?
I'm truly very sorry.
No, no, no.
No, no, no. Just hang on a minute.
This… This is ridiculous.
You can't just do this to us.
What are we supposed to do now?
We'll reach out to you very soon.
Moeno's being called a scammer
on the channel right now.
- It's the doctor's decision.
- Don't give us that bullshit!
- I'm sorry. That was her decision.
- You gotta do something.
How could you do this to me?
I am truly…
very, very sorry, Moeno.
It's way too late for that now, you know!
I know that I should have…
I should have told you about it sooner.
I knew at our first counseling session.
But I was…
I didn't trust myself.
I couldn't bring myself to say it.
I still don't get it.
Tell me why you can't do it!
I can't do it because…
…I know that
you weren't doing this for yourself.
I think you were trying
to get these surgeries for someone else.
Do you really want me
to perform this operation?
Mm.
Of course I want to, Doctor, I really do!
And since my dad's not here,
I'll be honest with you.
My views online have been
really struggling for a bit lately.
So then, when I got this offer,
I thought it was the perfect timing.
It would go viral, and I'd look cuter too!
It's so good! I trust you.
You were so cheerful.
Even though it's not a simple surgery,
you were acting
like it was nothing at all.
And I just got the feeling
that you were trying so hard
to be good for someone else.
How though?
How can you talk like you understand
how I'm feeling inside?
You're not me, Dr. Rin!
I am though.
Moeno, I am
exactly like you.
Hey.
This might finally be it for the director.
What? You think so?
I mean, this was the chairman's project,
and now she's botched it all.
- Ah.
- Mm.
You know,
I've got to say, I feel relieved.
SNACK BAR ITTENBARI
Just so you know…
I'm not gonna quit.
And I don't expect you to understand, Mom.
But from now on, I'm not gonna
interfere with your life either.
Why don't we leave it at that?
ESTABLISHING A CHILDREN'S CLINIC
PROPOSAL ON FUTURE MANAGEMENT POLICY
It's strange, isn't it,
for a daughter
to disregard her father's opinion?
How does it feel
to have someone
bite the hand that feeds her?
PROPOSAL ON FUTURE MANAGEMENT POLICY
Damn it.
How could she make a fool out of me?
How dare she make a fool out of me?!
How could she do it?
Why did she do it?!
Why?!
Oh, damn it!
It looks like the Moenon Channel
is going to be starting a collaboration
project with a different clinic.
Can you tell me which clinic it is?
It'll be with MBC.
That's it, then.
If she's made peace with it,
I can't do anything now.
- Why don't we jump in with counselling?
- Mm. Great.
So tell me, Moeno,
what kind of face would you like to have?
- I thought about it.
- Mm-hmm.
- And I didn't mention this before…
I thought about a face
that I'd really like to have, ideally.
Oh, whose face is it?
Mm.
This face right here.
Oh!
She's very beautiful.
- Isn't she?
- Mm.
- Is that your mom?
- Yes, that's my mom.
I can tell.
- You look a lot like her.
- Really? Yay!
Yeah.
Tell me, what part
of your mom's face do you like most?
- Her eyes.
- Oh yeah?
Your eyes…
What? No way!
Mom?
Mom!